### **Profile**

Self-driven, high energy, highly motivated, experienced sales and marketing professional with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunication industry. Accumulated a great deal of experience in B2B & government sales, account management, direct & indirect sales, distribution support, trade marketing, market research and geo-marketing. Interested in (KPIs & ROI).

Skills in customer service, Pre-& after Sales, meeting sales goals, closing skills, prospecting skills, Negotiation, self-confidence, product knowledge, presentation skills, client relationships, motivation for sales.

# Experience

B2B SALES SENIOR ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE, ZAIN TELECOM, SULAIMANI (APR 2014 —PRESENT)

Generate corporate and government sales in the Sulaymaniyah & Erbil region. Manage client portfolio and generated new clients via constant visits, sales calls, presentations, follow ups with potential and existing customers. Ensure department objectives goals such as client retention, development and maintenance.

Manage client's relationship (Client's visits reports, deliveries, claim, services, technical support, ... etc.)

Invoicing process and documentation to Clients in coordination with Finance and Warehouse.

Follow up on customer collection in order to ensure the commitment of clients to pay on time.

Focus on our existing clients for increase revenue of company.

Work closely with Zain technical team to bridge the gap between client requirements and Zain business solutions.

Working with another departments (Operation, Planning, Marketing, Finance& Legal) for provide best service to our Clients and solving all problems in short time.

Work supporting to Zain Cash team and share Zain Cash offers with our existing clients with follow up and push for closing the deal.

Work supporting to consumer sales team and manage their sales team when they have new product and share the products with corporate and government in Erbil And Sulaymaniyah.

Market survey about B2B offers & product, meeting with clients about their problems and needs. After survey work closely with B2B Marketing team about create solutions for customers.

Work closely with B2B marketing team for evaluate and create offers and find solution case by case according to needs of customers and ROI.

# TRADE MARKETING TEAM MEMBER, ZAIN TELECOM, SULAIMANI

(SEPT 2012 - APR 2014)

Support to direct and indirect sales teams, finding new POS (point of sales) locations. Determine which POS's are eligible for promotions and promotional material. Distribute marketing material of offers to POS's. Weekly visits to 100+ locations to maintain POS standards.

Conducted market survey, monitor competition by gathering market place information such as price, products and merchandising material.

Correction and update for database of Consumer sales Department with our daily visits (Information of more than 700 POS).

Supported the distribution, market research and geo-marketing teams.

Provide training to distribution's Salesman and Sub dealers about our products and commission.

#### **AUDITOR AND SALES SUPPORT, TAWOON COMPANY, SULAIMANI**

(SEPT 2011 - SEPT 2012)

Supported sales by providing historical records by maintaining records on area and customer sales. Collected sales and visit reports from sales team. Audit on Sales team with visits to point of sales. Create new Sales process and finding new channels and zones for sales. Support and plan to marketing team for promotion to product.

#### COORDINATOR, RIOM TRANSPORTS TRAVAUX PUBLIC, SULAIMANI

(APR 2010 - SEPT 2011)

Follow up and support to the logistic process from Dubai to company location (Sulaymaniyah), And coordinate with origin team about transferring the product from Dubai to Iran And Iraq, coordinate with border and check points in Kurdistan, and translator of Persian & Arabic Language.

## Education

2018, attained a Bachelor of Computer Engineering-Information Technology Degree, from Ilam University in

2012, attained an Electronic Diploma, from Sulaymaniyah Polytechnic University in Iraq.

### Skills

Selling Skills: Generating leads, qualifying leads, sales pitch, negotiations and closing the deal.

Computer Skills: Microsoft office suite, Microsoft Dynamics CRM, Smartsheet and various computer programming languages.

Flexibility: Work outside the standard working hours to get the deal done, such as meetings on weekends and after hours. Ability to travel when needed.

### Languages:

Kurdish NativeEnglish Good

Arabic Very Good

• Persian Native

# **Certifications/Training Courses**

2020, Time Management, Sulaymaniyah

2020, Keys of Success, Sulaymaniyah

2020, Helping Clients Succeed, Online (Franklin Covey)

2020, Filling Pipeline Training, Baghdad (Franklin Covey)

2019, Marketing Communication, Online

2019, Sales Coaching, Online

2019, Product Management and Customer Development, Online

2019, Soft Skills for Sales Professionals, Online

2019, Balanced Scorecard and Key Performance Indicators, Online

2019, Sales Closing Strategies, Online

2019, B2B Marketing foundation, Online

2019, Sales Handling Objections, Online

2019, Business Development Foundations, Online

2019, Business to Business Sales Course, Online

2019, Selling Skill Training, Erbil

2018, Communication Skills Training, Erbil.

2017, Microsoft Dynamics CRM Training, Baghdad.

2014, Key account management & Sales training, Beirut (Informa)

2012, Trade marketing field force training, Erbil.

Références

Available upon request.